  {
    id: 286,
    question: 'Where is the tallest tower in Europe?',
    mapType: 'sat',
    type: 'trivia',
    textAnswer: 'The [Ostankino Tower](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ostankino_Tower) in Moscow, Russia, stands at 540m tall and completed in 1967.',
    answers: [
      {
        type: 'exact',
        lat: 55.819722,
        lng: 37.611667,
      },
    ],
  },

  {id: 288, question: "Where is London?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.514248, lng: -0.093145,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 289, question: "Where is Birmingham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.466667, lng: -1.916667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 290, question: "Where is Manchester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.5, lng: -2.216667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 291, question: "Where is Leeds?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.8, lng: -1.583333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 292, question: "Where is Sheffield?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.366667, lng: -1.5,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 293, question: "Where is Glasgow?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.833333, lng: -4.25,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 294, question: "Where is Newcastle upon Tyne?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.988056, lng: -1.619444,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 295, question: "Where is Nottingham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.966667, lng: -1.166667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 296, question: "Where is Liverpool?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.416667, lng: -3,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 297, question: "Where is Southend-on-Sea?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.533333, lng: 0.7,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 298, question: "Where is Bristol?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.45, lng: -2.583333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 299, question: "Where is Edinburgh?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.95, lng: -3.2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 300, question: "Where is Brighton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.833333, lng: -0.15,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 301, question: "Where is Bradford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.783333, lng: -1.75,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 302, question: "Where is Leicester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.633333, lng: -1.133333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 303, question: "Where is Sunderland?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.911944, lng: -1.383333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 304, question: "Where is Belfast?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.6, lng: -5.933333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 305, question: "Where is Portsmouth?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.766667, lng: -1.083333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 306, question: "Where is Bournemouth?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.716667, lng: -1.883333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 307, question: "Where is Middlesbrough?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.572778, lng: -1.162778,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 308, question: "Where is Coventry?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.416667, lng: -1.55,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 309, question: "Where is Southampton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.9, lng: -1.4,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 310, question: "Where is Reading?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.433333, lng: -1,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 311, question: "Where is Sutton on Hull?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.783333, lng: -0.316667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 312, question: "Where is Blackpool?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.816667, lng: -3.05,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 313, question: "Where is Plymouth?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.396389, lng: -4.138611,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 314, question: "Where is Luton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.883333, lng: -0.416667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 315, question: "Where is Oxford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.75, lng: -1.25,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 316, question: "Where is Norwich?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.633333, lng: 1.3,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 317, question: "Where is Old Aberdeen?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 57.166667, lng: -2.1,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 318, question: "Where is York?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.966667, lng: -1.083333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 319, question: "Where is Dundee?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56.5, lng: -2.966667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 320, question: "Where is Ipswich?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.083333, lng: 1.166667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 321, question: "Where is Peterborough?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.583333, lng: -0.25,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 322, question: "Where is Cambridge?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.2, lng: 0.116667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 323, question: "Where is Exminster?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.683333, lng: -3.483333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 324, question: "Where is Bath?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.379444, lng: -2.365556,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 325, question: "Where is Chester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.2, lng: -2.916667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 326, question: "Where is Greenock?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.933333, lng: -4.75,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 327, question: "Where is Carlisle?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.883333, lng: -2.933333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 328, question: "Where is Scarborough?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.287222, lng: -0.414167,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 329, question: "Where is Ayr?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.45, lng: -4.616667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 330, question: "Where is Inverness?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 57.466667, lng: -4.233333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 331, question: "Where is Perth?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56.4, lng: -3.433333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 332, question: "Where is River?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.133333, lng: 1.266667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 333, question: "Where is Dumfries?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.066667, lng: -3.55,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 334, question: "Where is Omagh?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.60124, lng: -7.29085,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 335, question: "Where is Penzance?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.113611, lng: -5.547778,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 336, question: "Where is Fort William?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56.816667, lng: -5.116667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 337, question: "Where is Kirkwall?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 58.966667, lng: -2.95,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 338, question: "Where is Wick?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 58.433333, lng: -3.083333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 339, question: "Where is Lerwick?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 60.15, lng: -1.15,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 340, question: "Where is Ilford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.559666, lng: 0.070805,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 341, question: "Where is Chelmsford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.733333, lng: 0.483333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 342, question: "Where is Weston-super-Mare?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.345833, lng: -2.967778,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 343, question: "Where is Llangefni?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.266667, lng: -4.333333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 344, question: "Where is Southport?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.666667, lng: -3,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 345, question: "Where is Armagh?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.34812, lng: -6.64957,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 346, question: "Where is Rochester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.383333, lng: 0.516667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 347, question: "Where is Rochdale?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.616667, lng: -2.15,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 348, question: "Where is Motherwell?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.783333, lng: -4,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 349, question: "Where is Clydach Vale?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.626667, lng: -3.476111,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 350, question: "Where is Kirkintilloch?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.916667, lng: -4.166667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 351, question: "Where is Stirling?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56.116667, lng: -3.95,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 352, question: "Where is Lambeth?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.5, lng: -0.116667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 353, question: "Where is Dungannon?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.50333, lng: -6.76427,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 354, question: "Where is Huddersfield?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.65, lng: -1.783333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 355, question: "Where is Stretford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.45, lng: -2.316667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 356, question: "Where is Preston?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.766667, lng: -2.716667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 357, question: "Where is Newbury?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.4, lng: -1.316667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 358, question: "Where is Rhuthun?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.116667, lng: -3.3,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 359, question: "Where is Blackburn?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.75, lng: -2.483333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 360, question: "Where is Wood Green?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.6, lng: -0.116667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 361, question: "Where is Stafford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.8, lng: -2.1,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 362, question: "Where is Gloucester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.833333, lng: -2.25,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 363, question: "Where is Glenrothes?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56.2, lng: -3.183333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 364, question: "Where is South Bank?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.566667, lng: -1.15,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 365, question: "Where is Pont-y-pŵl?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.701111, lng: -3.044444,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 366, question: "Where is Durham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.766667, lng: -1.566667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 367, question: "Where is Bedford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.133333, lng: -0.45,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 368, question: "Where is Taunton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.021111, lng: -3.104722,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 369, question: "Where is Widnes?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.35, lng: -2.733333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 370, question: "Where is Uxbridge?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.55, lng: -0.483333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 371, question: "Where is Elgin?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 57.65, lng: -3.333333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 372, question: "Where is Hove?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.833333, lng: -0.183333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 373, question: "Where is Lewes?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.866667, lng: -0.016667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 374, question: "Where is Maidstone?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.266667, lng: 0.516667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 375, question: "Where is Llandrindod Wells?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.233333, lng: -3.383333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 376, question: "Where is Kingston upon Hull?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.716667, lng: -0.333333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 377, question: "Where is Kingston upon Thames?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.416667, lng: -0.283333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 378, question: "Where is Barri?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.406667, lng: -3.269444,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 379, question: "Where is Giffnock?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.8, lng: -4.283333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 380, question: "Where is Hounslow?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.466667, lng: -0.35,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 381, question: "Where is Derry?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.99899, lng: -7.31063,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 382, question: "Where is Newtownabbey?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.66912, lng: -5.904435,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 383, question: "Where is Forfar?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56.65, lng: -2.883333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 384, question: "Where is Torquay?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.45, lng: -3.5,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 385, question: "Where is East Ham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.533333, lng: 0.05,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 386, question: "Where is Solihull?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.416667, lng: -1.783333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 387, question: "Where is Poplar?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.5, lng: -0.016667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 388, question: "Where is Mold?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.166667, lng: -3.133333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 389, question: "Where is Warwick?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.283333, lng: -1.583333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 390, question: "Where is Knowsley?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.45, lng: -2.85,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 391, question: "Where is Hwlffordd?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.801667, lng: -4.970833,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 392, question: "Where is Rotherham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.433333, lng: -1.35,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 393, question: "Where is Caernarfon?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.15, lng: -4.266667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 394, question: "Where is Morpeth?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.166667, lng: -1.683333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 395, question: "Where is Irvine?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.6, lng: -4.666667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 396, question: "Where is Cwmbran?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.653056, lng: -3.026667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 397, question: "Where is Stornoway?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 58.216667, lng: -6.366667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 398, question: "Where is Darlington?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.533333, lng: -1.566667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 399, question: "Where is Hackney?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.55, lng: -0.05,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 400, question: "Where is Trowbridge?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.318889, lng: -2.208611,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 401, question: "Where is Merthyr Tudful?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.75, lng: -3.383333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 402, question: "Where is Hertford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.8, lng: -0.066667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 403, question: "Where is Newry?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.17795, lng: -6.33807,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 404, question: "Where is Belfast?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.59682, lng: -5.92541,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 405, question: "Where is Camberwell?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.473619, lng: -0.091618,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 406, question: "Where is Caerfyrddin?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.859167, lng: -4.311667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 407, question: "Where is Cookstown?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.6428, lng: -6.74519,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 408, question: "Where is Dorchester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.716667, lng: -2.433333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 409, question: "Where is Port Talbot?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.6, lng: -3.783333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 410, question: "Where is Antrim?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.71291, lng: -6.20846,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 411, question: "Where is Gateshead?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.945, lng: -1.6175,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 412, question: "Where is Wandsworth?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.45, lng: -0.2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 413, question: "Where is Exeter?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.7, lng: -3.533333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 414, question: "Where is Camden Town?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.545664, lng: -0.140308,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 415, question: "Where is Alloa?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56.116667, lng: -3.8,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 416, question: "Where is Chicksands?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.033333, lng: -0.366667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 417, question: "Where is Banbridge?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.35091, lng: -6.26701,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 418, question: "Where is Walthamstow?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.6, lng: -0.033333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 419, question: "Where is Paisley?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.833333, lng: -4.433333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 420, question: "Where is Chichester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.833333, lng: -0.783333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 421, question: "Where is Craigavon?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.44966, lng: -6.36457,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 422, question: "Where is Woolwich?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.466667, lng: 0.2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 423, question: "Where is Northallerton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.333333, lng: -1.433333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 424, question: "Where is Romford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.583333, lng: 0.2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 425, question: "Where is Walsall?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.6, lng: -2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 426, question: "Where is Scunthorpe?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.583333, lng: -0.65,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 427, question: "Where is Islington?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.533333, lng: -0.1,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 428, question: "Where is Oldbury?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.5, lng: -2.016667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 429, question: "Where is Downpatrick?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.32694, lng: -5.71134,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 430, question: "Where is Livingston?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.883333, lng: -3.533333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 431, question: "Where is Ashton-under-Lyne?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.5, lng: -2.1,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 432, question: "Where is Winchester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.016667, lng: -1.316667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 433, question: "Where is Sandbach?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.133333, lng: -2.366667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 434, question: "Where is Derby?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.933333, lng: -1.5,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 435, question: "Where is Twickenham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.433333, lng: -0.316667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 436, question: "Where is Saint Helens?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.45, lng: -2.733333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 437, question: "Where is Bury?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.6, lng: -2.3,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 438, question: "Where is Maidenhead?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.516667, lng: -0.7,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 439, question: "Where is Wembley?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.55, lng: -0.283333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 440, question: "Where is Hartlepool?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.686111, lng: -1.2125,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 441, question: "Where is Hugh Town?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 49.914597, lng: -6.314273,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 442, question: "Where is Oldham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.55, lng: -2.116667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 443, question: "Where is Bexleyheath?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.45, lng: 0.15,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 444, question: "Where is Ebbw Vale?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.783333, lng: -3.2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 445, question: "Where is Magherafelt?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.75426, lng: -6.60941,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 446, question: "Where is Wigan?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.533333, lng: -2.616667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 447, question: "Where is Ballymena?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.86121, lng: -6.27633,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 448, question: "Where is Halifax?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.716667, lng: -1.85,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 449, question: "Where is Stockport?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.4, lng: -2.15,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 450, question: "Where is Stockton-on-Tees?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.583333, lng: -1.416667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 451, question: "Where is Northampton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.25, lng: -0.883333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 452, question: "Where is Grays?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.483333, lng: 0.333333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 453, question: "Where is Ystrad Mynach?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.640278, lng: -3.243333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 454, question: "Where is Aberaeron?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.25, lng: -4.25,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 455, question: "Where is Newtown Saint Boswells?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.583333, lng: -2.683333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 456, question: "Where is Enfield?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.666667, lng: -0.066667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 457, question: "Where is Stoke-on-Trent?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53, lng: -2.183333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 458, question: "Where is Sutton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.35, lng: -0.2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 459, question: "Where is Dudley?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.5, lng: -2.083333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 460, question: "Where is Wrecsam?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.05, lng: -3,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 461, question: "Where is Aberdeen?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 57.133333, lng: -2.1,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 462, question: "Where is Bolton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.583333, lng: -2.433333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 463, question: "Where is Warrington?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.383333, lng: -2.6,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 464, question: "Where is Salford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.483333, lng: -2.266667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 465, question: "Where is Kensington?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.504699, lng: -0.199827,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 466, question: "Where is Doncaster?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.533333, lng: -1.116667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 467, question: "Where is Swindon?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.516667, lng: -1.783333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 468, question: "Where is Pen-y-Bont ar Ogwr?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.505833, lng: -3.577222,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 469, question: "Where is Catford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.45, lng: -0.016667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 470, question: "Where is Coleraine?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.13489, lng: -6.66873,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 471, question: "Where is Barnsley?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.55, lng: -1.483333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 472, question: "Where is Caerdydd?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.5, lng: -3.2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 473, question: "Where is Poole?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.716667, lng: -2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 474, question: "Where is Bracknell?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.416667, lng: -0.75,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 475, question: "Where is Wakefield?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.7, lng: -1.483333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 476, question: "Where is Thornbury?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.608889, lng: -2.520278,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 477, question: "Where is Wokingham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.416667, lng: -0.833333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 478, question: "Where is Falkirk?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56, lng: -3.766667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 479, question: "Where is Haddington?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.933333, lng: -2.766667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 480, question: "Where is Abertawe?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.633333, lng: -3.966667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 481, question: "Where is Beverley?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.833333, lng: -0.416667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 482, question: "Where is Croydon?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.383333, lng: -0.1,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 483, question: "Where is South Shields?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.987778, lng: -1.421389,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 484, question: "Where is Morden?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.398217, lng: -0.19837,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 485, question: "Where is Lochgilphead?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 56.033333, lng: -5.416667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 486, question: "Where is Worcester?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.2, lng: -2.2,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 487, question: "Where is Matlock?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.133333, lng: -1.533333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 488, question: "Where is Shrewsbury?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.716667, lng: -2.733333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 489, question: "Where is Truro?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.261667, lng: -5.043333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 490, question: "Where is Hereford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.05, lng: -2.716667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 491, question: "Where is Newport?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.583333, lng: -2.983333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 492, question: "Where is Oakham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.666667, lng: -0.733333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 493, question: "Where is Milton Keynes?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.033333, lng: -0.7,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 494, question: "Where is Dagenham?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.55, lng: 0.166667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 495, question: "Where is Conwy?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.283333, lng: -3.833333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 496, question: "Where is Dalkeith?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.866667, lng: -3.066667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 497, question: "Where is Enniskillen?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.3466, lng: -7.64114,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 498, question: "Where is Hamilton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.766667, lng: -4.033333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 499, question: "Where is Hendon?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.6, lng: -0.216667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 500, question: "Where is Hammersmith?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.5, lng: -0.233333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 501, question: "Where is Bromley?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.4, lng: 0.05,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 502, question: "Where is Telford?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.633333, lng: -2.5,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 503, question: "Where is Harrow?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.583333, lng: -0.316667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 504, question: "Where is Ealing?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.488802, lng: -0.30479,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 505, question: "Where is Slough?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.5, lng: -0.583333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 506, question: "Where is Wolverhampton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 52.583333, lng: -2.133333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 507, question: "Where is Dumbarton?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.95, lng: -4.566667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 508, question: "Where is Bangor?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.66166, lng: -5.66545,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 509, question: "Where is Wallsend?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.991389, lng: -1.559722,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 510, question: "Where is Strabane?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.8224, lng: -7.46844,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 511, question: "Where is City of Westminster?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.5, lng: -0.116667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 512, question: "Where is Lincoln?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.233333, lng: -0.533333,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 513, question: "Where is Newport?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 50.7, lng: -1.3,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 514, question: "Where is Lisburn?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 54.50991, lng: -6.0404,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 515, question: "Where is Aylesbury?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 51.816667, lng: -0.8,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 516, question: "Where is Wallasey?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.433333, lng: -3.066667,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 517, question: "Where is Grimsby?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 53.533333, lng: -0.05,}], type: "ukcities",},
    {id: 518, question: "Where is Kilmarnock?", answers: [{type: "exact", lat: 55.633333, lng: -4.533333,}], type: "ukcities",},
